HAFIZ ELFIA WEDO PUTRA



Contact

Address:

KOMP. PCI BLOK E 27 A NO. 02 Cilegon, Banten 42423

Place /date of Birth:

Cilegon, June 22, 2000

Phone:

+62 87724006119

Status:

Single

Email:

hafizelfiawedoputra@outlook.com

Website:

hafizewp22.github.io

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/hafizewp/

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia English

Fluent Elementary

Hard Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- Java
- ReactJS
- Laravel
- Android Studio (Java)
- MySQL / SQL
- Database Design
- Figma (Software)
- Data Analysis

Soft Skills

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time Management

Summary

I have experience in web development at my internship company and I am interested in technology. I am also a hard worker, have integrity, responsibility and work in a team. Really likes to learn coding such as UI/UX, websites and data analysis to create interesting programs.

Experience

Web Developer - PT. Telkom Indonesia

Internship

March 2022 - Present

This section serves as a Web Developer to help companies check and update/create websites using Laravel and ReactJS.

Student Mentor - Bina Nusantara University

 Friends Care Community - Peer Partner October 2021 – February 2022

The task is to help friends who have special attention and high concern for disability issues and special needs on campus.

Organization – Bina Nusantara Computer Club (BNCC)

Learning and Training (LnT) Staff
 August 2020 – February 2022
 Establish curriculum and class materials and schedules for classes and teaching. And create and do attendance for each LnT class.

Organization - Bina Nusantara Computer Club (BNCC)

Activist

September 2019 – August 2020

Student Leadership and Management Exercises (LKMM). And training and learning to create Website design (HTML & CSS).

Education

Bachelor's Degree: Computer Science, 2019 - Present

Bina Nusantara University, Jakarta, ID

Streaming: Database Technology, GPA: 3,23 / 4,0

Vocational School: **Software Engineering,** 2016 - 2019 **Vocational High School of Informatics,** Serang, ID

Score: 81 / 100

Certificates

- Introduction to HTML5 (University of Michigan)
- HTML Course by Sololearn
- Learn to Code with Python by Udemy
- Database Design by Oracle Academy
- Database Design and Programming with SQL
- Web Development Path (Node.js) by Progate
- Database Coaching by Course-Net Indonesia, B+
- Java (Basic) by HackerRank
- Problem Solving (Basic) by HackerRank

Honors & Awards

2021 - Designing UI/UX with Figma Competition Bina Nusantara University 3rd Winner - Campus level

2020 - Asia Jakarta - Indonesia National Contest (INC) 2020 International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) 70th ranking of 700 teams - National level

2018 - Sister School 3 - Student Exchange To Thailand Student exchange to one of the best schools in Bangkok, Thailand, namely Matthayom Watnairong School and exchange of culture, language and new knowledge and cooperation between the two schools.

Research

2021 - Augmented Reality for Human Digestive Anatomy Biology Learning

Augmented Reality Technology research for 5 months, through Augmented Reality applications that have been made and then tested on teachers and students in high school, and the results of the research are successful.